<index image="front_left.png" back="front_panel.xml">
<title>Front Left Side</title>
<!-- Miscellaneous Panel -->
<area shape="rect" coords="208,493,235,521" title="Autopilot Roll Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>HDG SEL - Autopilot turns the aircraft to capture and maintain the heading selected by the heading reference marker on the HSI, as set by the HDG knob.</li><li>ATT HOLD - Autopilot maintains roll attitude.</li><li>STRG SEL - Autopilot steers aircraft to the selected steerpoint.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="261,487,286,520" title="Autopilot Pitch Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>ALT HOLD - Engages both pitch and roll autopilot control: maintain constant altitude and maintain roll as determined by the settings on the ROLL switch.</li><li>A/P OFF - Disengages pitch and roll axes of autopilot.</li><li>ATT HOLD - Engages both pitch and roll autopilot control: maintain constant pitch attitude and maintain roll as determined by the settings on the ROLL switch.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="248,429,279,461" title="Terrain Following ADV Mode Indicator" impl="yes"><ul><li>The ADV mode indicator refers to the Terrain Following system which is set through the TFR page of the MFD.</li><li>ACTIVE - Illuminates when the TFR is enabled.</li><li>STBY - Illuminates when the automatic terrain following system (ATF) is ready to take over.</li><li>Note: While the indicators work, Terrain Following is not fully implemented (use with caution).</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="261,378,286,408" title="Master Arm Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>MASTER ARM - The FCC and SMS are able to enter weapon delivery modes. Arm and release of stores is enabled.</li><li>OFF - All ordinance systems are safetied and release is inhibited except for emergency jettison.</li><li>SIMULATE - The FCC and SMS are able to enter weapon delivery modes. Arm and release of stores is inhibited.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="circ" coords="292,339,10" title="Alternate Release Button" impl="yes"><ul><li>Duplicates the function of the Weapon Release (pickle) button on the stick.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="247,293,271,322" title="Laser Arm Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Arms the Targeting Pod designation and ranging lasers for firing.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="circ" coords="291,286,10" title="ECM Light" impl="yes"><ul><li>Illuminates green when consent for ECM transmit is present (JAMMER on).</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="277,214,303,242" title="Run Silent Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Allows control of the RF emission.</li><li>NORM - Normal RF operations.</li><li>QUIET - FCR, AIFF, IECM, and TACAN do not transmit.</li><li>SILENT - FCR, AIFF, IECM, TACAN, CARA, and TFR do not transmit.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="poly" coords="300,178,317,178,317,474,307,495,304,533,192,533,192,484,215,462,234,387,243,278,256,278,263,219" title="Miscellaneous Panel" />
<!-- Side Buttons -->
<area shape="poly" coords="403,27,429,50,378,105,354,81" title="MASTER CAUTION Light" impl="yes"><ul><li>Illuminates shortly after an individual light on the Caution Panel illuminates, indicating a malfunction or specific condition exists.</li><li>It does not illuminate in conjunction with the Warning Lights.</li><li>May be reset by depressing the face of the light.</li><li>Unless it is reset the MASTER CAUTION light will remain illuminated as long as the individual Caution Light is illuminated.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="poly" coords="313,128,332,146,316,165,296,147" title="Terrain Following System Failure Warning Light" impl="yes"><ul><li>TF-FAIL - Indicates a failure in the terrain following system. Illuminates if RF SILENT is selected and TF radar is on.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="poly" coords="284,158,299,173,284,189,269,175" title="(F-ACK) Fault Acknowledge Button" impl="yes"><ul><li>Recall and acknowledge Pilot Fault List (PFL) display entries.</li><li>The AVIONICS FAULT, ENGINE FAULT, and FLCS FAULT Caution Lights may be reset with the F-ACK button (by viewing the relevant PFLs).</li></ul></area>
<area shape="poly" coords="234,250,256,253,253,276,231,273" title="IFF Identification Button" impl="no"><ul><li>IFF IDENT - The primary method of initiating the identification-of-position function of the IFF system.</li></ul></area>
<!-- Radar Warning Receiver (RWR) -->
<area shape="rect" coords="446,30,599,183" title="Radar Warning Receiver (RWR)" impl="yes"><ul><li>Display symbols that represent tracking radar signals from SAMS, AAA, Aircraft radar, etc.</li><li>Symbols are displayed on the scope according to their type, bearing, and prioritized threat status (the higher the threat status, the closer to the center of the outer, middle, and inner rings).</li></ul></area>
<!-- Threat Warning Buttons -->
<area shape="rect" coords="405,76,434,106" title="Handoff Button" impl="yes"><ul><li>Handoff is used to set the mode of operation of the RWR.</li><li>There are 4 modes of operations: Normal, Diamond Float, Transient, and Latch.</li><li>The modes are selected by differing presses and holds of the button. Please refer to the Operators Manual for further information.</li><li>The bottom light of the indicator is illuminated as soon as power is applied.</li><li>The top indicator is illuminated only when a handoff mode is engaged (Diamond Float, Transient, and Latch).</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="372,108,402,138" title="Launch Warning Light" impl="yes"><ul><li>Flashes ON at 4Hz as soon as the EWS detects a radar-controlled missile launch has been detected.</li><li>The indicator is backed up by audible warning tone.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="405,108,434,138" title="Priority Mode Button" impl="yes"><ul><li>When the MODE button is pressed the RWR displays only the 5 most important symbols instead of the usual 12 symbols (16 when UNKNOWN mode is selected).</li><li>The RWR enters PRIORITY mode and the top light of the indicator is illuminated.</li><li>The bottom light OPEN is then extinguished as both lights are mutually exclusive.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="339,140,369,170" title="Unknown/Naval Threat Button" impl="yes"><ul><li>The indicator has three lights instead of two: U (top), ship symbol (center) and UNKNOWN (bottom).</li><li>When pressed the top (U) and bottom (UNKNOWN) lights are illuminated and the RWR displays unknown symbols. It can then also display 16 symbols instead of the usual 12. The unknown mode is deselected by pressing the push button and the top and bottom lights are extinguished.</li><li>Naval threats are usually put at a lower priority than air or ground threats. Press (right click) to make naval threats an increased priority. The ship symbol is illuminated when in NAVAL mode.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="372,140,402,170" title="System Test Button" impl="no"><ul><li>When pressed performs BIT and illuminates top light.</li><li>The bottom light is illuminated as soon as power is applied.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="405,140,434,170" title="Target Separate Button" impl="yes"><ul><li>When unpressed, the RWR shows all threats at their true azimuth relationship to your aircraft.</li><li>When pressed, the top light (TGT SEP) illuminates and the lower-priority threats are moved radially away from the center on the RWR for 5 seconds allowing you to see the display of higher-priority threats more easily.</li><li>After that time, the RWR reverts to normal and the top light extinguished.</li><li>The bottom light is illuminated as soon as power is applied.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="poly" coords="429,49,443,49,443,188,324,188,324,159" title="Threat Warning Prime Panel"><ul><li>Manages the information displayed on the RWR.</li><li>It is made of 6 square lights all featuring a push button except the Missile Launch indicator.</li><li>Each indicator (except the Missile launch indicator) has multiple lights on the top and bottom.</li><li>The bottom light illuminates when the system is powered and the top light illuminates depending on the status of the relevant system (except the Missile launch indicator).</li></ul></area>
</index>
