<index image="right_panel_g.png" back=".">
<title>Right Console Panel G</title>
<!-- Sensor Power Management Panel -->
<area shape="rect" coords="308,18,331,48" title="Left Fuselage Hardpoint Power Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>LEFT HDPT - Power on the left fuselage hardpoint (normally HAD).</li><li>OFF - Power off the left fuselage hardpoint.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="356,18,380,48" title="Right Fuselage Hardpoint Power Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>RIGHT HDPT - Power on the right fuselage hardpoint (normally TGP).</li><li>OFF - Power off the right fuselage hardpoint.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="404,18,427,48" title="Fire Control Radar (FCR) Power Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>FCR - Powers up the FCR.</li><li>OFF - Powers down the FCR.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="452,18,476,48" title="Radar Altimeter Power Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>RDR ALT - Power on the radar altimeter.</li><li>STBY - Set the radar altimeter to standby.</li><li>OFF - Power off the radar altimeter.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="268,1,524,67" title="Sensor Power Management Panel" />
<!-- HUD Remote Control Panel  -->
<area shape="rect" coords="305,79,329,110" title="HUD Scales Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls display of various HUD scales.</li><li>VV/VAH - Displays vertical velocity, velocity, altitude, and heading scales; roll indicator above the FPM.</li><li>VAH - Displays velocity, altitude, and heading scales; roll indicator below the heading tape.</li><li>OFF - All scales off except for digital readout windows for velocity, altitude and heading; roll indicator below the heading.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="359,79,383,110" title="HUD Attitude Bars/Flightpath Marker Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls flightpath marker (FPM) symbology.</li><li>ATT/FPM - Displays the FPM and the attitude reference bars.</li><li>FPM - Displays the FPM and removes the attitude reference bars.</li><li>OFF - Removes the attitude reference bars and the FPM.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="413,84,437,110" title="HUD DED/PFL Display Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls the display of either the DED or PFL data in the HUD window.</li><li>DED - DED data.</li><li>PFL - PFL data.</li><li>OFF - Neither.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="462,83,486,110" title="Depressible Reticle Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls selection of the primary and standby manual bomb aiming reticles.</li><li>STBY - Selects the standby reticle and removes all other symbology (this option is available even if the HUD fails).</li><li>PRI - Selects the primary reticle and does not remove all other symbology.</li><li>OFF - No reticle selected.</li><li>The reticle is moved downward on the HUD with the Reticle Depression Control Knob on the ICP.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="305,149,329,173" title="Velocity Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls the selection of the three aircraft velocity scales in the HUD.</li><li>CAS - Calibrated airspeed.</li><li>TAS - True airspeed.</li><li>GND SPD - Ground speed.</li><li>Note that if the gear is lowered while Ground speed is selected, the HUD airspeed reverts back to CAS.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="359,149,383,173" title="Altitude Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls the selection of the three aircraft altitude scales displayed on the HUD.</li><li>ALT RADAR - Radar altitude (AGL).</li><li>BARO - Barometric altitude (MSL).</li><li>AUTO (mislabeled OFF) - Displays radar altitude while below 1500 ft AGL and barometric altitude when higher than 1500 ft AGL.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="413,149,437,173" title="Brightness Control Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls HUD brightness.</li><li>DAY - Ranges from off to full intensity.</li><li>AUTO BRT - Automatically maintains a specified symbol-to-background contrast level.</li><li>NIGHT - Ranges from off to half intensity.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="463,149,488,173" title="Test Switch" impl="no"><ul><li>Displays four HUD test patterns.</li><li>STEP - Cycles between patterns.</li><li>ON - Displays the first test pattern.</li><li>OFF - No test pattern.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="268,68,524,186" title="HUD Remote Control Panel " />
<!-- Interior Lighting Control Panel -->
<area shape="circ" coords="323,238,21" title="Primary Consoles Brightness Adjustment Knob" impl="no"><ul><li>Varies the backlight brightness of the right and left auxiliary and primary consoles.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="circ" coords="396,238,21" title="Primary Instrument Panel Brightness Adjustment Knob" impl="Controls backlighting for all panels"><ul><li>Varies the backlight brightness of the instrument panel.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="circ" coords="469,238,21" title="Data Entry Display Brightness Adjustment Knob" impl="yes"><ul><li>Varies the brightness of the DED and PFLD.</li><li>When fully left, turns off the DED.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="circ" coords="322,337,25" title="Consoles Floodlights Brightness Intensity Knob" impl="Controls the intensity of the floodlights throughout the cockpit"><ul><li>Varies the intensity of the floodlights shining on the right and left auxiliary and primary consoles.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="circ" coords="402,342,20" title="Instrument Panel Floodlights Brightness Intensity Knob" impl="no"><ul><li>Varies the intensity of the floodlights shining on the main instrument panel.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="457,329,482,354" title="Malfunction and Indicator Lights Intensity Switch" impl="no"><ul><li>Controls the light intensity of all the warning, caution, and indicator lights except the following individually-dimmed lights: AOA indexer, AR/NWS indexer, DED, ECM control panel, MFDs, PFLD, TWS indicators.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="268,187,524,388" title="Interior Lighting Control Panel" />
<!-- Environmental Control System Control Panel -->
<area shape="circ" coords="354,439,24" title="Temperature Knob" impl="no"><ul><li>Controls the temperature of the cockpit.</li><li>OFF-COOL-AUTO-WARM - Set air condition automatically between off, cold and warm.</li><li>OFF-COOL-MAN-WARM - Set air condition manually between off, cold and warm.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="circ" coords="461,440,28" title="Air Source Knob" impl="yes"><ul><li>Controls the source of air used for pressurizing/ ventilating the cockpit, G-suit, and fuel tanks.</li><li>OFF - Engine bleed air valves close and all pressurizing functions shut off.</li><li>NORM - Air conditioning set for normal temperature and pressure regulation.</li><li>DUMP - Cockpit pressure dump valve opens to atmospheric pressure.</li><li>RAM - Engine bleed air valves close. Cockpit pressure dump valve opens. All pressurizing and temperature control functions shut off. The ram air valve opens to ventilate the cockpit and avionics.</li></ul></area>
<area shape="rect" coords="268,389,524,490" title="Environmental Control System Control Panel" />
<!-- Nuclear Consent Switch -->
<area shape="rect" coords="542,128,592,162" title="Nuclear Consent Switch" impl="no"><ul><li>Guarded, three position toggle switch.</li><li>ARM REL - Allows Nuclear ordinance to be armed and dropped, providing consent has been received.</li><li>OFF (Safe) - Does not allow Nuclear ordinance to be dropped.</li><li>REL ONLY - Allows Nuclear ordinance to be dropped but not armed, this being used to jettison the Nuclear ordinance in emergencies.</li></ul></area>
<!-- Crypto-Radio (CRAD) Switch -->
<area shape="rect" coords="546,228,571,254" title="Crypto-Radio (CRAD) Switch" impl="no"><ul><li>Works in conjunction with the KY-58 Secure Voice System.</li><li>CRAD 1 - UHF radio encrypted via KY-58.</li><li>PLAIN - No radios encrypted.</li><li>CRAD 2 - VHF radio encrypted via KY-58.</li></ul></area>
<!-- Zeroize Switch -->
<area shape="rect" coords="170,199,222,233" title="Zeroize Switch" impl="no"><ul><li>Guarded, three position toggle switch.</li><li>OFP - Zeroizes DTC, FCC, MMC, GPS, mode-4, IDM, PDG and RWR.</li><li>DATA - Zeroizes DTC, GPS, mode-4, MMC and IDM.</li><li>Seat ejection automatically performs an escape zeroize operation.</li></ul></area>
<!-- Voice Message System Inhibit Switch -->
<area shape="rect" coords="198,438,224,464" title="Voice Message System Inhibit Switch" impl="yes"><ul><li>INHIBIT - Allows the suppression of VMU aural messages.</li></ul></area>
</index>
